insightsforliving.org 2018-12-02

# Privacy Policy | INSIGHTSFORLIVING

**Our Privacy Policy**

Last updated July 26, 2018

Welcome to our online community (“platform”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). Our solemn pledge is to protect your personal information and acknowledge your right to privacy. To that extent, this policy explains the ways we manage user data on all our platforms (websites, mobile applications, services, sales, and all events registration). If you have any questions about our policy, please contact us at [optout@covenantchristiancentre.org](mailto:optout@covenantchristiancentre.org).  We will appreciate if you take time to read through carefully before using any of our platforms. If there are any terms that you do not agree with, please discontinue the use of our platform and services.

  1. **Personal information to be provided**

We collect personal information that you provide to us such as name, password, email address, phone number, contact information, payment information, social media login data, geo-location, mobile device, etc.

We get some of the information when you register on our platform, show interest in obtaining information about us or our products and services, when you participate in our programme or otherwise when you contact us.

Sometimes, you will have the option of not supplying certain information. The extent of information you supply to us determines the interaction you get. The kind of information we require includes:

**Your Name and Contact Details:**  The required information may include your first name, middle name, last name, and other names, e-mail address, and telephone number. In some cases, some of the required information may be mandatory in which case you may not be allowed to engage in the activity that requires those information and you may therefore not be able to take advantage of the special features and functions which are meant for those who have supplied the mandatory information.

**Security details:**  We collect passwords, password hints, and similar security information used in authenticating and accessing your account with us. We also collect data necessary to process your payment when you transact on our platform. Such data include credit card number, security code for authenticating transactions etc.

**Social Media Login Data.**  You will have the option of registering on some of our platforms using your social media account details. If you opt to register with any of your social media accounts, we will have access to information about you from your social media provider. The Information we receive about you depends on the social media provider concerned. In general, they may include your names, phone number, profile picture, friend list, email address and other information you choose to make public.

**Certain Information are automatically collected when you visit our platform. Information like** _IP  address,  device information, browser, language preference, country, location, _operating system, referring URLs, information about your use of our platform that you visit etc. This information helps us principally with analytics, security analysis, and aid user experience.

You may be asked to provide certain information when you use our App platforms. We may request that you permit us to access your location. Our request is in most cases to enable you enjoy location specific services.

We may also request for access to certain features on your device such as your device’s bluetooth, reminder, calendar, messages, camera, social media accounts, and other features.

We may automatically collect device information (such as your mobile device ID, model and manufacturer), operating system, version information and IP address. We may also request to send you push notifications regarding your account or the mobile application.

You may visit your device settings to alter our access to any of the information.

**Other platforms where we collect information include** _public databases, marketing  partners, social media platforms,  and other outside sources. The information collected on the platforms are however limited to your information on those platforms._

  2. **Use of your information**

We will not share your Personal Identifiable Information with any third party except as provided in this Agreement. Since some of our services depend on our synergy with Authorised Third Party Service Providers or partners who sometimes perform certain functions on our behalf, we may share your information with such Authorised Third Party Service Provider. By supplying us with your personal identifiable information, you have conceded to share your details with our Affiliates or third party service provider, and have agreed to exempt us from any form of liability arising from the use of your information by such Authorised third party service provider as we do not have the legal power to regulate their use of your personal information.

Generally, we use your Information to:

  * **To aid account creation and logon process.** If you choose to link your account with us to a third party account *(such as your Google or Facebook account), we use the information you allowed us to collect from those third parties to facilitate account creation and logon process.
  * **To give you updates on information as they relate to our programmes, services, activities, events, updates, feedbacks, announcements, advertisements and conferences**
  * **To register you for our programmes, services, activities, events or conferences and to provide services requested by you.**
  * To raise fund and process donations etc.
  * **To fulfill our legal obligations, enforce our terms, conditions and policies and also protect our platforms from fraud etc.**.
  * **To enable user-to-user communications**. Some of our platforms (e.g. prayer cell platform) enable other users to interact with you. We may therefore use your information to advance that functionality

  3. **Confidentiality of information shared us**

As a law abiding entity, we may share your information where necessary to abide by the law, protect us, and to protect others where the demand is more highly placed. We may also share your information in keeping with this policy, and our other conditions of use.

  4. **Cookies and Other Computer Information**

So as to safeguard and identify you whenever you are logged on to our platform, you will be assigned a permanent “cookie” which will automatically be stored on your computer’s hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit our platform so that we can enhance and customize your online experience.

You may choose to browse on our platform without cookies, but without these, you will not be able to take advantage of certain unique features of our Platform.

While we acknowledge our limitations in guaranteeing 100% safety of your information, we will keep updating our security measures to safeguard your information. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your information and privacy, we do not promise or guarantee that your information will always be private and safe and are therefore not responsible for the actions of any third party that may access such information.

  5. **Information from people below 18years (Minors)**

Our mode of operation is based on the properties of the internet, we do not intentionally collect personal information about minors or other persons without full civil or contractual capacity, we therefore recognize our limitation at dealing with and distinguishing the age or capacity of the users. By using or accessing any of our platforms, you certify that you have the involvement of a parent or guardian or otherwise, that you are a person over 18 years old with full capacity and ability to form a legally binding contract in the jurisdiction in which you are resident or in which you are using or accessing our platform. Accordingly, we are excluded from any liability whatsoever arising as a result of the limited or restricted civil and contractual capacity of the users. If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of the terms of this Agreement, do not use any of our Platforms.

If a minor or other person does not have full civil or contractual capacity and has provided personal information to us without the proper consent of their parent or legal guardian, such parent or legal guardian should contact us to remove such personal information.

_ _ You may choose to review or delete your account at any time and we will upon receipt of notification of the occurrence carry out your instruction.

  6. **Do we make updates to this policy?**

This Privacy policy will be updated from time to time to reflect changes with best practices or when necessary to meet present users feedback and changes in our services.

We suggest you visit regularly to keep yourself abreast of any changes made to this policy.

**Additional Privacy Terms or Notices**  
In addition to this Privacy Notice, there may be specific campaigns or promotions which will be governed by additional privacy terms or notices. We encourage you to read these additional terms or notices before participating in any such campaigns or promotions as you will be required to comply with them if you participate. Any additional privacy terms or notices will be made prominently available to you.

  7. **Downloads**

Any files downloaded from our Site or App are strictly at user’s own risk

  8. **How long do we retain your personal data**?  
We will keep your personal data for as long as it is required and in accordance with the purpose it is being processed for or legal requirements. We will keep the personal data for a period which enables us to handle or respond to any complaints, queries or concerns relating to our relationship with you.

Your data may also be retained so that we can continue to improve your experience with us and to ensure that you receive any loyalty rewards which are due to you.

You may also notify us whenever you no longer wish to hear from us and will keep minimum information upon receipt of such notice to ensure that no future contact is made by us.

We retain the identifiable data we collect directly for targeting purposes for as little time as possible, after which we employ measures to permanently delete it.

We will actively review the personal data we hold and delete it securely, or in some cases anonymise it, when there is no longer a legal, business or user need for it to be retained.

  9. **How can you contact us about this policy?**

Covenant Christian Centre Chief Privacy Officer can be contacted a by email optout@covenantchristiancentre.org

When a privacy question or access request is received we have a dedicated team which communicates with the contact and seek to address the specific concern or query which is raised. Where your issue may be more substantive in nature, more information may be sought from you, so we would reach you. If you ask us, we will endeavour to provide you with information about relevant complaint avenues which may be applicable to your circumstances.

Any question or comment about this policy, data processing or if you would like to make a complaint about a possible breach of local privacy laws, should be communicated by sending an e-mail or submitting a request through the “Contact Us” form on our websites or email optout@covenantchristiancentre.org

**Disclaimer of Liability, Damages and Responsibility:**

By this Policy we do not represent or warrant the condition or functionality of our platform(s), its suitability for use, nor guarantee that service will be free from interruption or any error. No liability or responsibility shall lie for risks associated with the use of our site, including but not limited to any risk to your computer, software or data being damaged by any virus, software, or any other file that might be transmitted or activated via our website or your access to it. Neither do we guarantee the reliability of information contained on our platform- particularly those shared by third party users.

**Account Information**

If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can Contact us using the contact information provided.

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, or comply with legal requirements.

**Copyrights and Trademarks:**

Copyright (c) Covenant Christian Centre 2018  All Rights Reserved

All material on this website is copyrighted by Covenant Christian Centre except for some material that is copyrighted by others and used here by permission. Copyrighted material may not be copied, reproduced or otherwise used for commercial purposes without the written permission of the copyright holder. This site also contains some trademarks, which may not be appropriated by persons other than the trademark owner and may not be used contrary to trademark law. If you wish to request permission to use materials in a manner otherwise prohibited by this Agreement, please send an email to: optout@covenantchristiancentre.org.
